http://dawsonbooks.com/index.php/privacy-policy/

Our website address is: http://dawsonbooks.com
Dawson’s Book Shop / Michael Dawson Gallery does not share Personal Information of any users of its Site with any other users and takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally identifiable and personally identifiable information.
Cookies
A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. Dawson’s Book Shop / Michael Dawson Gallery may use cookies to help identify and track visitors, their usage of the Site, and their website access preferences. Site visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using our website, with the drawback that certain features of the Site may not function properly without the aid of cookies.
Changes to this Privacy Policy
This Privacy Policy is effective as of June 21, 2019 and will remain in effect except with respect to any changes in its provisions in the future, which will be in effect immediately after being posted on this page.
We reserve the right to update or change our Privacy Policy at any time and you should check this Privacy Policy periodically. Your continued use of the Service after we post any modifications to the Privacy Policy on this page will constitute your acknowledgment of the modifications and your consent to abide and be bound by the modified Privacy Policy.
Contact Us
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at:
Michael [at] dawsonbooks.com
